<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IMCI</string>
    <string name="dummy_text">IF YES, ASK:LOOK, LISTEN, FEEL: • Count the breaths in one minute. • Look for chest indrawing. • Look and listen for stridor or wheeze • For how long? NOTE: Child must be calm</string>
    <string name="dummy_text_2">AND IF WHEEZE, ASK: •Has the child had a wheeze before this illness? •Does the child have frequent cough at night? •Has the child had a wheeze for more than a week? •Is the child a known asthmatic?</string>
    <string name="diarrhoea_text">IF YES, ASK: • For how long? •If diarrhoea for 14 days or more, has the child lost weight? •Is there blood in the stool? •What treatment is the mother giving.? LOOK OR FEEL: •Look at the child’s general condition. Is the child: - Lethargic or unconscious? - Restless and irritable? •Look for sunken eyes •Offer the child fluid.Is the child: - Not able to drink or drinking poorly? - Drinking eagerly, thirsty? •Pinch the skin of the abdomen. Does it go back: - slowly? - or very slowly? (more than 2 seconds) CLASSIFY DIARRHOEA:</string>
    <string name="diarrhoea11">•Lethargic or unconscious •Sunken eyes •Not able to drink or drinking poorly •Skin pinch goes back very slowly.</string>
    <string name="diarrhoea12">Two of the following signs: 1)Restless, irritable 2)Sunken eyes 3)Drinks eagerly, thirsty 4)Skin pinch goes back slowly</string>
    <string name="diarrhoea13">Not enough signs to classify as severe or some dehydration</string>
    <string name="fever">the child have fever (By history, or temperature 37.5° C or above )</string>
    <string name="fevert_text">IF YES, ASK: • For how long? • If more than 7 days, has fever been present every day? LOOK AND FEEL: •For stiff neck and bulging fontanelle. •Look for other causes of fever</string>
    <string name="fever_text2">THEN DECIDE THE CHILD’S MALARIA RISK: Malaria Risk means: Lives in Malaria zone or visited a malaria zone in the previous month. If in doubt, also classify for malaria. • Do a rapid malaria test if available</string>
    <string name="feverbtn21">• Any general danger sign OR • Stiff neck OR •Bulging fontanelle.• Any general danger sign OR • Stiff neck OR • Bulging fontanelle.</string>
    <string name="feverbtn22">• No general danger signs and •No stiff neck or bulging fontanelle</string>
    <string name="feverlisttext">SUSPECTED MENINGITIS Give first dose of ampicillin IM or ceftriaxone IM (p.13) Test the blood sugar, then treat or prevent low blood sugar (Page 14) Give one dose of paracetamol for fever 38°C or above (p.10) Refer URGENTLY</string>
    <string name="earproblemtext">IF YES, ASK: •Is there ear pain? •Is there ear discharge? If yes, for how long? LOOK AND FEEL: •Look for pus draining from the ear. •Feel for tender swelling behind the ear. =</string>
    <string name="malnutrition_growth">ASK: Has the <i>child</i> lost weight? LOOK and FEEL: = GROWTH Plot the weight on the growth chart: • Is the child: −Low weight (below 3rd centile) −Very low weight (below 60% of expected weight) Look at the shape of the weight curve: •Is the child: −Gaining weight well? −Gaining weight but curve is flattening? −Losing weight ? •Look for visible severe wasting •Feel for oedema of both feet</string>
    <string name="hiv_text">IF THE CHILD- •has a classification today of PNEUMONIA or PERSISTENT DIARRHOEA or NOT GROWING WELL OR •Has had an episode of persistent diarrhoea in the past three months OR •Has had a discharging ear at any time OR •If the mother is known to be HIV positive NOTE (as above): Does the child have •any PNEUMONIA now? •ear discharge now OR in the past? •low weight for age? •poor weight gain or weight loss? •Any episode of persistent diarrhoea in the past three months? LOOK AND FEEL FOR: •enlarged lymph glands in two or more of the following sites: neck, axilla or groin? •oral thrush? •parotid gland enlargement?</string>
    <string name="treat_text">TEACH THE MOTHER TO GIVE ORAL DRUGS AT HOME =======Follow the general instructions below for every oral drug to be given at home. Also follow the instructions listed with each drug’s dosage table. Determine the appropriate drugs and dosage for the child’s age or weight Tell the mother the reason for giving the drug to the child Demonstrate how to measure a dose Watch the mother practise measuring a dose by herself Ask the mother to give the first dose to her child Explain carefully how to give the drug Advise the mother to store the drugs safely Explain that all the tablets or syrup must be used to finish the course of treatment, even if the child gets better Check the mother’s understanding before she leaves the clinic</string>
    <string name="teachmother_text">Explain to the mother what the treatment is and why it should be given Describe the treatment steps listed in the appropriate box Watch the mother as she does the first treatment in the clinic (except remedy for cough or sore throat) Tell her how often to do the treatment at home. If needed for treatment at home, give mother a small bottle of gentian violet or nystatin Check the mother’s understanding before she leaves the clinic</string>
    <string name="CLINIC_text1">􀂾Explain to the mother why the drug is given 􀂾 Determine the dose appropriate for the child’s weight (or age) 􀂾 Measure the dose accurately NOTE: immunise every sick child as needed</string>
    <string name="clinic_text2">GIVE EMERGENCY TREATMENTS IN CLINIC ONLY 􀂾Explain to the mother why the drug is given 􀂾 Determine the dose appropriate for the child’s weight (or age) 􀂾 Use a sterile needle and sterile syringe when giving an injection 􀂾 Measure the dose accurately</string>
    <string name="followup_text1">Care for the child who returns for follow-up using ALL the boxes that match child’s previous classifications. If the child has any new problem, assess, classify and treat the new problem as on the ASSESS AND CLASSIFY chart.</string>
</resources>
